{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "______ is the number of individuals of a species in a given area",
      "answers": [
        "Limiting Factor",
        "Living Population",
        "Native Population",
        "Invasive Species"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "_____ is a species that was brought into an ecosystem by human intervention, by accident or on purpose.",
      "answers": [
        "Limited Population",
        "Introduced Predators",
        "Introduced Species",
        "Invasive Species"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Introduced species are more often _________, than _________.",
      "answers": [
        "Harmful, Helpful",
        "Peaceful, Disruptive",
        "Helpful, Harmful",
        "Disruptive, Peaceful"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "What are the three classifications of Floridaâ€™s ecosystems?",
      "answers": [
        "Wetland, Dry Land, Mixed Land",
        "Land, Freshwater, Marine",
        "Freshwater, Saltwater, Mixed Land",
        "Wet Land, Dry Land, Freshwater"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "What animal lays its eggs in isolated and developed beaches?",
      "answers": [
        "Turtles",
        "Pythons",
        "Alligators",
        "Iguanas"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "What is a native species to Florida that has been endangered for many years?",
      "answers": [
        "Florida Alligator",
        "Florida Panther",
        "Florida Black Bear",
        "Burmese Python"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "_____ is a threat to the Florida Panther.",
      "answers": [
        "Wolves",
        "Black Bear",
        "Burmese Python",
        "Alligators"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "What makes the Burmese Python a threat to the Florida Panther?",
      "answers": [
        "They are an introduced species",
        "They reproduce quickly and with lots of offspring",
        "They have very few predators",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "_____ is an introduced species that has wiped out massive quantities of native fish populations.",
      "answers": [
        "Alligator",
        "Lionfish",
        "Sea Turtle",
        "Sea Otter"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "Identify the native species to Florida?",
      "answers": [
        "Florida Panther",
        "Lionfish",
        "Burmese Python",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "Florida officials monitor which of the following species?",
      "answers": [
        "Florida Panther",
        "Lionfish",
        "Burmese Python",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "Why should the Florida Panther be monitored by Florida officials?",
      "answers": [
        "They do so for every predator species",
        "Low population numbers",
        "Large population numbers",
        "They interact with humans frequently"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "How can introduced species populations be managed?",
      "answers": [
        "Prevent bringing animals to different ecosystems",
        "Capture animals and release them in their natural ecosystems",
        "Have people regularly monitor ecosystems for new, introduced species",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    }
  ]
}
